

# Sirvan Doukchi

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## **Career Summary**

Full stack developer, with hands-on IT experience, passionate motivated to actualise ideas all the way to implementing in browsers in a userfriendly and modern interface. I am resourceful, and committed to continually advancing my knowledge of relevant technologies including JavaScript, React JS/Native, HTML and CSS, Ruby on Rails, Node.JS and more.

### Contact



Sydney, NSW



0406 471 \*\*\*



SirvanSh@gmail.com



www.Sirvan.Dev



@sirvan-doukchi



https://github.com/SirvanD

# **Skills**

#### Languages

- JavaScript
- · Node.js
- Ruby
- CSS/SCSS

### Database/Cloud

- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Firebase
- AWS

#### **Techs**

- Docker
- · Jira Workflow
- Github Actions
- Adobe Photoshop
- MS Azure
- CISCO CCNA

#### Frameworks/Libraries

- · React.js
- NextJS
- · Sinatra/PG
- Bootstrap 5
- · Material UI

# **Software Engineering Projects**

#### Servo App



- JavaScript
- Node JS / Express
- Google Maps Api
- **Government provided DB**
- **PostgreSQL**
- **Bootstrap 5**
- Deployed to Heroku

### Space Watch www



- Node JS
- **User Authentication**
- OMDBI API
- CRUD actions
- Deployed to Heroku

#### **BookShelf**



- React
- NodeJS / Express
- MongoDB for Database
- **Firebase Authentication**
- Material UI
- · Google Books API and **REST API**

#### Tic Tac Toe www



- JavaScript
- DOM manipulation
- Vanilla JavaScript
- · CSS / Bootstrap

# Work Experience

Clayton UTZ Law Firm

**IT Support Analyst** 

Dec 2020- Sep 2021

Active directory administration, Microsoft Azure user groups, forest and domain management, shared drives, and application of SCCM, RDP, Logmein, and Skype remote consoles for assisting remote clients.

#### Melbourne Institue of Technology Oct 2019 - Dec 2020 **IT Support Officer**

Liaise with internal staff and students over the phone and on-site utilising HEAT ticket management for level 1 and 2 services and escalation of level 3 and security concerns to infrastructure

### **Education**

Software Engineering Immersive

#### **General Assembly**

Oct 2021 - March 2022

- · Creating full-stack applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, Express with Node.js, and Version Control (Git and GitHub)
- Integrated third-party APIs into websites and applications
- · Working via remote correspondence and learning new methods of research, communication and collaboration

#### Masters in Information and Communication Technology

#### University of Wollongong

Jul 2016 - July 2018

• Post graduated with a distinction average with key subjects: Project and Change Management, Systems Integration, Information Systems and strategy, Strategic network design, IT security and Risk Management.